David Schnibben

203 Marshview Dr. Richmond Hill, GA, 31324

Phone: 843-992-6283 E-Mail: schnibbend@gmail.com Website: web-students.armstrong.edu/~ds6225

Skills and Abilities

Technical abilities:

I am proficient with the following operating systems; Mac, Windows, IOS, Android. I have a fundamental background in following computer languages; C++, C#, JAVA, HTML, CSS.

Communication abilities:

Through my time in law enforcement I spent a vast amount of time writing reports of incidents for detectives to read latter. I was able to paint a clear picture of a scene on paper so that anyone reading my report, even years later in court, would be able to understand exactly what I had observed and what I did on any given scene.

Problem solving abilities:

As a Police Officer my main objective was to solve problems. I was able to quickly gain an understanding of any situation, however complex or stressful, and reach a solution that benefitted each party involved.

Experience

Montage Palmetto Bluff, Bluffton, SC Outside Golf Attendant	05-2016 to 01-2017
CaddieMaster, Bluffton, SC Caddie	09-2015 to 05-2016
Erica Herndon State Farm, Savannah, GA Sales Associate	01-2015 to 09-2015
Lexington County Sheriff's Department, Lexington, SC Deputy Sheriff	04-2013 to 11-2014
University of South Carolina Department of Law Enforcement, Columbia, SC Police Officer	05-2011 to 03-2013
City of Columbia Police Department, Columbia, SC Police Officer	06-2008 to 05-2011

Education

Armstrong State University, Savannah, GA Information Technology with a concentration in Cyber Security	Anticipated Graduation May 2017
University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC BS in Criminology and Criminal Justice	Graduation May 2008

Schnibben Page 1 last update 1-2017